Where are we going?
We're joining a mixer.
They're so kind.
I didn't want them
to feel forced to like me.
What I want isn't something like that.
Why don't you open up to them like this?
Tell them you're feeling confused,
and tangled up inside.
I'm sure they'll understand.
What misunderstanding?
I didn't want you to "like" me out of pity,
and not actually feel that way.
I...
I want to be with you whenever I can.
What do you mean when you "like" me?
I want to touch you.
I also want to hold hands with you.
I want to hug you tight, too.
That's what my "like" means.
See you soon, Kou.
[Morning]
[Are you still asleep?]
[I had a dream about you last night]
[What time should we head out today?]
[You're awake]
[Morning]
I'm heading out.
Hello, I'm your boyfriend.
I know.
And you are?
Your boyfriend.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
What time does your shift end today?
I'll be doing work until the evening.
Sorry.
Huh?
We just started dating, and I'm so busy...
I'll be waiting for you to finish.
Okay.
- It's strange.
- Huh?
I thought my love for you maxed out,
but now that we're dating, I love you more.
Oh, uh...
I don't know how to respond.
Too heavy?
No, not at all...
Your bag.
I'll carry it for you.
Thanks.
I'm racking up "boyfriend points".
If I get to ten, I get a kiss.
See you later.
I'm walking you in, not trespassing.
Whatever you say.
I'm charging up till the evening.
What am I, an energy drink?
Mayama.
Now?
Now.
I'll come get you once you're done.
See you later.
Bye for now.
That's playing dirty.
Thanks.
Are you free next Saturday?
Why?
Check it out.
A Tanabata Festival.
[T/N: July 7th; known as the Star Festival]
It's happening by your place, right?
Yeah.
I can't believe it's almost July.
Want to go together?
Hold on.
- Is that a no?
- No, but...
I knew it.
I'm scheduled to work at an event that day.
- I see.
- I'm free the day after.
Let's find another festival to go to.
Sorry, I'm only free that Saturday.
I have summer school the rest of our break.
My Mayama battery will run out...
Sorry.
Nah, I share the blame there.
It'd be nice if we could do something
that screams "summer".
For real?
- Loser pays the bill.
- Deal.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Puppy!
Come take a break.
- Great work out there.
- Thank you.
It's so hot in here...
I'd bet.
- Here, stay hydrated.
- Thank you.
I didn't think the "event"
would be a Tanabata festival.
When you're ready, could you pass out
these wishing slips to guests?
- Sure.
- Thank you so much!
You must be melting in there.
No one wanted to wear the suit,
but someone had to do it.
I'm glad you volunteered.
I put the slips right there for you.
This was the festival where it happened.
What are you talking about?
Dude, obviously we were joking.
She'd never confess to a guy like you.
I remembered something I'd rather forget.
Thanks.
Asamiya?
Thank you!
Why is he here?
I told him I couldn't go today.
Kou!
Sheesh, don't leave me behind.
Huh?
Say what?
He spoke.
Where to go...
Hey, let's grab a wishing slip.
I'm good.
What? Buzzkill.
Could I get a wishing slip?
Hello?
Thank you.
I feel like he's staring daggers into me.
You're imagining things.
If you say so.
Come on, let's go see the stalls.
I'm craving shaved ice.
Do you want some?
Festivals are great.
I really feel like I'm back in Japan now.
Thanks for coming with me.
What's her relationship with Asamiya?
I was so worried about you
while I was abroad.
Really now.
- They're here?
- Yeah.
They're looking this way.
Was he using me forget the loneliness
of his girlfriend being overseas?
Was I just the substitute until she returned?
I know what you consider your faults.
But all that has made me
fall for you even more.
I obviously meant it romantically.
No. Asamiya would never do that.
I should ask him about her first.
Huh? Mayama?
Kagami...
I haven't seen you in ages.
What's with the getup?
Holy cow.
Are they still there?
Nope. They're gone.
Hey, did I just hear a sigh?
You wish you had a cute girlfriend like me.
That's some self-confidence.
You know, I feel bad
for whoever was in that suit.
They must be melting.
I know someone who'd immediately
volunteer for something like that.
Wait, him?
Yeah. He's the one
who fell for that confession.
I laughed so hard, my stomach hurt!
I'd never work here if I were you.
Yeah, seriously.
Hey, you're not in a festive mood.
- I am.
- You should let him have a date.
- Yeah!
- What? Why?
We wanna lift Mayama's spirits.
What?
I'm already dating someone right now.
- What?
- No way.
- You're lying.
- Yeah.
Come on, don't be shy.
Just take a lap around the festival.
Sounds good to me.
Yeah, go for it!
Kagami.
What?
Don't be such a killjoy, go.
- Yeah.
- She's waiting.
No.
Huh?
I don't want to.
You say you were just joking.
But that really hurt my feelings.
I don't want to see you guys anymore.
- Huh?
- What gives?
We're your only friends, so suck it up.
I have other friends now.
Ones who actually care.
Go with her. Now.
Don't touch him.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Mayama's friend. Unlike you jerks.
Huh?
Hey, ouch!
Don't mess with Mayama ever again.
Let's ditch these losers.
Yeah.
Mayama...
I'm glad you're okay.
Thank you.
Sorry.
I should have noticed sooner.
Did I gain extra "boyfriend points"?
Mayama?
Who was that?
Huh?
I saw you two going around together.
You and that pretty lady, arm-in-arm.
That's my...
Kou!
Jeez, there you are.
I was looking everywhere for you.
Huh? Who's this?
My friend, Mayama.
Thanks for tolerating my little brother.
I'm Kou's sister, Koiro Asamiya.
Huh?
Your sister?
We look nothing alike, right?
But you were walking with your arms linked...
Some girl has been coming onto me, hard.
She was following me around all day.
Yeah. So, I pretended to be his girlfriend.
I didn't think you'd see us.
So, that's what was going on.
Mayama, right?
Yes.
Take care of my brother for me.
I know he's a bit overbearing.
Not at all.
- Don't badmouth me.
- Sorry.
Oh, I know.
Here.
And here.
Go make a wish.
Go on.
Make a wish!
What did you write?
I'm not telling.
Aw, come on.
Where should I hang yours?
What did you write?
It's a secret.
If I tell you, it won't come true.
Then mine's a secret, too.
Our annual finale of the Tanabata Festival,
the fireworks show, is about to begin.
We hope it will serve as
a wonderful summer memory.
They're doing fireworks.
- Come with me.
- Huh?
I know the best viewing spot.
Hey, wait.
Slow down.
Are we walking any farther?
No.
We're here.
Look.
Wow...
I happened to find this spot
while running away in shame
from that whole confession prank.
These fireworks saved me in a way.
Doesn't it hurt to remember?
Not anymore. I have you now.
Let's watch the fireworks.
I'm glad.
We managed to do one "summer" thing.
[I wish for Mayama to find happiness]
[I wish to find happiness with Asamiya]
My sister's staying with a friend tonight.
My parents are on vacation,
and aren't home either.
Want to come over?
Huh?
Is that a no?
No, it's not exactly a no.
I'm not ready to let you go home yet.
I don't need to slam the breaks anymore.
Should we tell Sakaki
and Tsunekawada about us?
- I wouldn't want to...
- No.
We never know who's watching.
You never cared about that before.
Our relationship began with a seat change.
This romance
that began with one fateful seat change...
And you're okay with that, Asamiya?